chemedx.org 2015-12-22

# Privacy | Chemical Education Xchange

Chemical Education Xchange, [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/), recognizes that users may have concerns about privacy issues as they use [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/), [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/), and the services Chemical Education Xchange provides. Chemical Education Xchange is committed to providing users with a safe, secure environment in which to obtain information and use its services.

Chemical Education Xchange will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the information you provide remains private, and is used only for the purposes stated below. Please review the Terms of Use for the definition of the relationship between [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) and its users.

### Collected Information

Chemical Education Xchange collects information about the users of [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/). This information helps to determine the parts of the site visitors find most valuable as well as how to improve the services we provide. User identities remain anonymous unless the User provides this information as a part of registration.

Chemical Education Xchange records and may use your IP address to help diagnose problems and to administer our web site. Users may use [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) without registering, but registration must occur in order to use any personalization services or to take full advantage of our services. [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) registration forms require specific contact information: name, e-mail address, etc. The contact information may be used to contact users. Unique identifiers (such as IDs and passwords) are collected to verify the visitor's identity and for use in our record keeping.

### E-mail messages

Chemical Education Xchange communicates with its users by e-mail for specific web-related functions, such as password reminders. Because these messages are critical to site use, users will not be able to opt-out of receiving such messages.

Users who register with [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) or [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) may have the option of receiving occasional e-mails from us about new features and similar messages that we feel may be of interest. Users may opt-in to receive these messages. The following options are available to opt-out of receiving these messages if Users have previously opted-in:

  1. Edit User's registration profile
  2. Send e-mail to [chemedx](mailto:chemedx@chemedx.org)[@chemedx.org](mailto:jceAdmin@jce.divched.org)
  3. Send mail to Chemical Education Xchange, 209 N. Brooks St., Madison, WI 53715-1116
  4. Telephone to 800-991-5534 (toll free U.S, Canada) or 706-542-8523.

### Cookies

[www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) may use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie". A cookie is a small file that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive to identify you as a user. [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) do not use cookies to collect any personal information about users, nor do we sell or make them available to other organizations.

Disabling or deleting [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) or [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) cookies may prevent the web site from recognizing you as a previous user and may prevent you from using some features on the site. You may need to have cookies enabled to create an account at [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) or [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/).

### Security

Your account containing your information is password protected and should never be shared with anyone. [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

### Feedback

[www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) and [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/) encourage visitors to submit feedback and contribute to the content of Chemical Education Xchange. Any feedback that is submitted becomes the property of Chemical Education Xchange.

### Links to Other Sites

Chemical Education Xchange contains links to third-party web sites. Chemical Education Xchange is not responsible for the content or practices of linked third-party sites and does not make any representations regarding the content or the privacy pratices on such third-party web sites. Third-party web sites are accessed at your own risk. Please consult the privacy statements of such third-party web sites.

### Privacy Policy Updates

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted here so that visitors will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) or [www.jce.divched.org's](http://www.jce.divched.org%27s/) privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with [www.chemedx.org](http://www.chemedx.org/) or [www.jce.divched.org](http://www.jce.divched.org/), contact us at:

_Chemical Education Xchange_  
209 N. Brooks St.  
Madison, WI 53715-1116

telephone:  800-991-5534 (toll free U.S, Canada) or 706-542-8523

e-mail: [chemedx@chemedx.org](mailto:chemedx@chemedx.org)
